[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
NEIL : Come on , let 's find this grave .
I know he 's here somewhere .
Brody , come on , look for him .
Keep going . We 're gonna find him .
I know it 's here .
BRODY : It 's there !
NEIL : Over to the right . See over there ?
That 's it . There it is !
That 's it . All right !
This is it , all right . Let 's rip this sucker open !
I got to get a look at the main man !
[ LAUGHING ]
[ WHOOPING ]
NEIL : Come on , dig ! Deeper !
Come on , dig . Come on , let 's dig .
Come on , faster . Dig .
[ BRODY LAUGHING ]
Dig !
NEIL : Let 's just get all this dirt off , and then we 'll pry it open .
This is it . This is it .
Okay , let 's get it . Come on .
Come on !
Come on , pry this sucker open .
Pry .
Move it over here .
[ GRUNTING ]
NEIL : Harder . Come on .
Come on , Neil !
NEIL : Okay , here it comes .
[ BRODY LAUGHING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ GROANING ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
No . No , no !
[ SCREAMING ] No !
[ GASPS ]
[ PANTING ]
That must be the new kid .
Last stop . Everybody out .
Tommy ? Hey !
[ WHISTLES ]
No ? Beautiful . Sit there . I don 't give a shit .
Hey ! How you doing ?
Tommy Jarvis ?
Hi , my name is Pam Roberts .
I 'm the assistant director .
I 'm glad you 're here .
Well , if you 'd like to grab your things ,
I 'll take you in to meet the doctor , okay ?
Great .
Thank you .
Anytime , doll .
How was the ride ?
Come on , Tommy .
You okay ?
MATT : Come in .
Hi .
Hi , Tommy . I 'm Matthew Letter .
Welcome to Pinehurst . Have a seat .
Sit down , son .
What I 'm gonna do is tell you a little about Pinehurst ,
and then we 'll let you get settled in your room .
How does that sound ?
Tommy ?
Sure .
All right . About Pinehurst ,
you 'll find we 're very different from the state institution .
We don 't have any guards here .
Nobody 's gonna tell you what you can do or what you can 't do .
Basically , you 're your own boss .
It 's an honor system , Tommy .
What you 're really doing here , Tommy ,
is preparing yourself to re-enter society and start a new life .
So , Pam , you wanna point Tommy
toward his room and get him started ?
Sure . Okay ? All right , you go through the kitchen , up the stairs ,
and it 's the first door on your left , okay ?
I 'll see you in a bit .
[ EXHALES ]
So what do you think ?
The kid 's a real talker .
I noticed . How 'd they diagnose it ?
" Severe trauma at age 12 .
" Brutal self-defense murder of a psychopathic killer . "
Boy , they 've given him every treatment ,
every therapy they can think of .
It 's a wonder his mind isn 't fried
with all the drugs they 've given him .
[ GASPS ]
[ REGGIE LAUGHING ]
You scared of spiders ?
You scared of rubber spiders ?
You scared of rubber spiders on strings ?
Man , you are one scared cat .
Where I come from , you learn to be scared of nothing .
They call me Reggie the Reckless .
No spider will scare me .
[ GROWLS ]
Joke , man !
Don 't .
You don 't have to get all twisted out of shape about it .
I mean , you act like you made these things , or something .
I did .
Solid .
So you 're the new nut , huh ?
Is that what they call us ?
" Us " ? I ain 't one of you , man .
I 'm just visiting .
My granddaddy works here .
[ SIREN WAILING ]
Got to split . Catch you later . There 's action .
Joey , come on . Hurry , look .
[ WHOOPING ] Oh , my God !
Way to go , you guys ! Joey , come on .
[ GIRL LAUGHING ]
Stop , Grandpa ! Don 't !
Stop !
Hey , Matt . How 's it going ?
All right , Sheriff . What 's up ?
Well , Matt , you know , it 's like we talked about .
You got some neighbors who aren 't too happy about your place here .
Now , I certainly know what it is you 're trying to do ,
and I respect it , Matt , I do .
But , well , you see , we found a couple
of your kids on the Hubbard place again .
Deputy ! Yes , sir .
Bring them out .
Yes , sir .
[ LAUGHING ] Everybody out .
Cut out the fooling around . Fall in by ...
Yes , sir .
Just get moving , wise guy .
We found them in the Hubbard 's woods .
They were screwing their heads off , Matt .
I think we 're all pretty lucky this time ,
because Ethel didn 't see them .
I 'll take care of it , Sheriff .
[ MOTORCYCLE APPROACHING ]
I 'm gonna do the talking . You keep quiet .
Morning , Ethel .
My ! Don 't you look lovely today ?
Horseshit !
Now , Sheriff , you better hear me and hear me good .
I want this loony bin closed down .
Do you hear me , fellow ? Now , these kids ain 't nothing but trouble !
They don 't respect others property , and they 're all crazy !
You tell them , Ma !
Ethel , these kids weren 't doing ...
Doing ? Doing ?
You think I don 't know what those two perverts were doing in my yard ?
Say it like you mean it , Ma !
Would you shut the fuck up ?
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
Now , I 'm gonna tell all of you .
You mark my words , the next little bastard comes near my farm ,
I 'm gonna blow your fucking brains out . You hear me ?
Don 't you come near me , Sheriff . I 've warned you .
I 've got a bomb on me . I swear to you !
You make one move toward me , I 'm gonna blow us all up .
Start the engines , Junior .
That 's it . My final words .
Okay , okay , people , come on , let 's go . Party 's over .
She 's really something , ain 't she ?
Jeez .
But seriously , Matt , I 'd make an extra effort
to keep your kids off her property .
I will . Listen , by the way ,
I understand you got the Jarvis kid today .
Yeah , he arrived a little while ago .
And ?
And what ? Well , what 's he like ?
He 's like any other kid . He 's just ...
He 's been through a lot , that 's all .
Yeah . Well , good luck with him , pal .
Thanks a lot , Sheriff .
[ GRUNTING ]
Hi , girls .
Hi , Joey .
Hi , Violet . Huh ?
Hi !
What are you doing ?
Doing laundry , Joey .
Can I help ? I 'm really very good at doing laundry .
Matt never assigns it to me . I don 't know why .
Look , Joey , we really have to get this thing finished , okay ?
So I 'm here to help you .
You can count on me , Rob . You too , Vi .
Want a chocolate bar ?
Here , you want it ?
I 'll give you half , but I need half for later .
Piss off !
Please let me help you .
[ GASPS ] It 's really no problem ...
Joey ! Joey !
Will you just get out of here ? Fuck !
I 'm sorry , you two , really , I can do laundry great , but , well ...
If that 's how you feel , forget it .
I 'll just go help somebody else instead .
I 'll see you later .
Listen , if you change your mind , I 'll be right around , okay ?
Joey ! Joey !
VIOLET : Jesus , what a loser .
Look at this sheet .
I 'm not gonna wash it . You wash it .
Hi , Vic !
Get lost .
Come on ! Don 't be like that .
Let me help you with the wood today .
And anyway , I got two chocolate bars , see ?
Don 't tell the girls .
What an asshole .
You know , Vic , before I came here , I never had anything to do ,
me being an orphan and all .
People always teased me about
sitting around like some kind of pig or something .
But here , it 's different .
I can help others and do a lot of things .
You know something ?
I really love it here .
I hate it !
You know , to be perfectly honest with you ,
I never really chopped wood before ,
but it certainly looks like fun .
[ SHOUTING ] Leave me alone !
Here , Vic . Want a bite ?
Here , I 'll just put it over here ,
and later on , when you 're hungry , you can have it .
[ GRUNTING ]
Well , if that 's the way you feel , forget it , Vic ! Just forget it !
But I think you 're really out of line .
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SIREN WAILING ]
Yeah , we got a homicide on our hands .
See what you 've got on a Faden .
Victor J. Faden . F-A-D-E-N .
Thanks , Harriett .
[ POLICE RADIO CHATTER ]
[ GIRLS CRYING ]
Is there someone we should notify ?
As far as I know , there 's no immediate family .
His mother died while giving birth .
I don 't know what the hell happened to the father .
Took off somewhere , I guess .
The kid got shuffled around from home to home until he came here .
He was a good kid .
I know , Matt .
So , what have we got here ?
[ GASPS ] ROBIN : Oh , God .
PAM : It 's all right .
[ LAUGHS ] Bunch of pussies .
Come on , Roy . Get your hands dirty .
[ FLIES BUZZING ]
I 'm telling you , Pete , this is bullshit ! This really sucks !
Just do it . Fix it , man .
Those cunts aren 't gonna wait all night .
Oh , fuck ! This is a mess .
No way , I refuse to do this .
You 're the one who keeps fucking around with this thing ,
so get off your ass and you fix it !
You understand ?
Pete ?
[ HORN HONKING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
Fuck . You are an asshole !
What 's the matter , Vinnie ?
You scared of the dark ?
You all creeped out by that murder at the nuthouse ?
Yeah , sure . Look , as far as I 'm concerned ,
all those loonies should be killed off one by one .
Can you try it now ?
[ ENGINE STALLING ]
Jesus , man ! Can 't you do anything ?
Stop screwing around !
Get this done by the time I get back .
I gotta take a crap .
Crap , my ass !
Just do it , man ! I mean it .
Fucking asshole !
[ TWIG SNAPPING ]
You little fuck .
What are you doing , douchebag ?
Enough , already . You can stop .
Would you cut it out ?
Pete !
[ CHOKING ]
[ SINGING ]
All right , either you got the car started or you 're a dead man .
[ ENGINE STALLING ]
¶ This ain 't starting , man You fucked up again , it ain 't starting
¶ I 'm gonna kick your ass , kick your ass
¶ Come on , now Come on , everybody this ain 't starting
¶ Come on , motherfucker Fix the fucking car
¶ Come on You fucked up again , you asshole ¶
What you doing up there , Vinnie ?
[ SINGING ]
[ ENGINE RUNNING ]
[ WHOOPING ] All right . And we 're off . Let 's go !
[ GASPS ]
[ HORN HONKING ]
TOMMY : Die !
Die !
TRISH : Tommy !
TOMMY : Die !
TOMMY : Die ! Die !
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
Die ! Die ! Die !
TRISH : Tommy !
TOMMY : Die !
Die !
Die ! Die ! Die !
[ EXCLAIMS ]
[ CRYING ]
There you go .
Gramps .
What is it , son ?
Can I go see my brother ?
He 'll be in town tomorrow .
We 'll see . You know how I feel about that .
But , Gramps ...
I said we 'll see , Reggie .
[ CHUCKLES ]
Hey , come here , Reggie the Reckless .
Do me a favor , don 't kiss me when there 's people around , okay ?
Okay , it 's cool . Go and let everyone else know breakfast is ready .
You all ! Breakfast ! Come and get it !
I could 've done that .
I miss Joey already .
So do I.
Well , I hope Victor gets what 's coming to him .
Morning , everybody .
Morning . Morning .
Violet , you set too many places . Huh ?
I said , you set too many places .
No , I didn 't .
Yes , you did .
I don 't think Victor and Joey will be joining us this morning , Violet .
Or any other morning .
Reggie !
Oh , God . I 'm sorry .
[ STUTTERING ] You don 't set a place for a dead person .
I said I was sorry !
What 's going on here ?
Look , I know how you all feel .
This thing is not easy for any of us .
So let 's just have breakfast .
I 'm sorry , Vi , I was out of line .
Where 's Eddie ?
He 's upstairs .
Tommy , would you mind telling Eddie to come downstairs ?
Tommy ? Would you mind ?
Yeah , all right .
[ GROWLING ]
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
Relax , Chief . What 's wrong , no sense of humor ?
Can 't you take a joke ?
[ SCREAMING ]
It 's all right , Tommy ! It 's all right .
Just relax . It 's all right .
It 's all right . It 's gonna be all right .
Just relax . Yeah , it 's gonna be just fine .
I 'm gonna chop you into itty-bitty little pieces , my friend .
Just like they done to that piggo
over there at that fucking crazy farm .
[ SQUEALING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
You big dildo . Eat your fucking slop .
Ain 't I make the best goddamn stew in the whole wide world ?
Best goddamn stew in the whole wide world , Mama .
[ CHICKENS CLUCKING ]
It 's that goddamn coyote , gonna try to kill my lot again .
I 'm gonna show that bastard once and for all , you hear me , Junior ?
[ SLURPING ]
Holy shit ! Who the fuck are you and what the fuck do you want ?
Ma 'am , I ain 't eaten in two days . I 'd like to earn a meal .
Yeah ? What do you do ?
Whatever you need done .
Okay . Clean all the shit out of the chicken coop
and dump it behind the shed .
You come back here when you 've got all the shit out ,
and then I 'll fill your stomach .
Yes , ma 'am .
That is one fucking ugly man that goes there .
That 's one fucking ugly man , Mama .
Would you shut your trap ?
You know , you ain 't so pretty yourself , you know .
I ain 't so pretty myself , I know .
[ MUMBLING ]
[ SQUEALING ]
I want every inch of this area combed thoroughly .
Bring back anything you find , anything .
Get going .
Yes , sir .
What the hell 's going on here ?
You talking to me , Sheriff ?
I thought you was talking to me .
No , Roy . It 's okay .
Go ahead . Get them out of here .
Looks like we got us a maniac on the loose , huh , Sheriff ?
Yeah .
[ HORN HONKING ]
Lana ! Hey , Lana !
Sorry , buster . We 're closed .
It 's all right , I just want a take-out order .
You do ? Yeah .
Well , what would you like ?
I would like Lana to go with nothing on her .
And who wants her ?
The pride of the Unger Institute of Mental Health ,
who 's just dumped his last bedpan
and would like very much to party .
Will you get your ass out here ?
Lana ... I don 't know about that . I 'll have to ask her .
[ LAUGHS ] Hey , Lana . You want Billy ? You sure ?
She says she wants you , too .
But you have to wait a few minutes till she 's done inside .
[ EXCLAIMING HAPPILY ]
There . I 'm going to party .
[ GIGGLES ]
It 's show time !
[ HUMMING ]
That 's it .
That 's it . That 's the whole fucking thing right there .
There it is . You just stay right there , doll .
That 's just what the doctor ordered .
Nothing like a little preventive medicine .
And the forecast is cloudy in the mountains ,
sunny in the valleys , and snow flurries up your nose .
[ COUGHING ]
¶ I don 't know if he loves me
¶ But I think he does
[ GLASS BREAKING ]
Billy ?
Girl , you are so hot .
[ CAT SCREECHES ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ SIGHS IN RELIEF ]
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ HORN HONKING ]
Hey , Lana !
What the fuck is she doing ?
Hey !
Jesus Christ ! Come on , will you ?
Lana !
Hey ! Hey !
Bad kitty . You bad kitty .
I don 't like you anymore .
Kitty , I feed you , I love you , and you scare me like that .
Go on , kitty .
Sorry .
Billy ?
Billy , what are you doing ? It 's cold .
This is cute . I like this a whole lot .
You 're gonna waste a lot of money this way , smarty .
Oh , well , that just means more for me .
Yummy .
Oh , my God . Billy ! Billy ! Billy ?
[ CRYING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ LAUGHING ]
[ HEART BEATING ]
[ HEARTBEATS FADE ]
COBB : I don 't care if you have to put
your fucking mother behind bars !
Get me the goddamn psycho who 's responsible for this mess .
I mean , shit , Tucker , what the hell 's going on here ?
I mean , this is a small town , man .
And small towns are supposed to be safe .
I know who it is .
What ?
I said , I know who it is .
Who ?
It 's Jason Voorhees .
Jason Voorhees ?
You 're out of your fucking mind !
You 've been out in the sun too long .
Jason Voorhees is dead !
His body was cremated . He 's nothing but a handful of ash .
You know that for sure , Mayor ?
Were you there ? Did you see him cremated ?
Jason Voorhees . Yes .
I can 't believe this !
Here , this is your Jason Voorhees , here . This .
Your ass is on the line here , Tucker .
Are you getting that ?
You get me a goddamn live suspect !
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
[ STIFLED SCREAMING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
You fuck ! You really scared me .
You loved it .
You want more ?
Eddie , we can 't .
Matt will kill us .
Fuck him .
Fuck you .
Exactly . Fuck me .
Come on , baby .
Come on . Come on .
Come on ! You 're so slow . God !
[ EXCLAIMING ]
[ SCREECHING ]
Come on .
Watch the dirt . Watch the dirt .
Whoa !
What ?
Wait . Wait a minute .
Especially for the occasion .
[ TINA GIGGLING ]
[ BOTH MOANING ]
[ GROANS ]
I should go wash up .
Okay , sugar .
[ GIGGLING ]
Hurry back .
I 'm hurrying .
[ SCREAMING ]
I 'm back .
What is this ? Sleeping ?
[ GASPS ]
[ GROANING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
Let 's get this show on the road !
Wait a minute , Reggie , I 'm coming .
I just don 't understand it .
Now , Reggie , I want you to be a good kid with Pam .
She 's doing us both a great favor .
Yeah , if she ever gets here .
And don 't go getting into any trouble with Demon , you hear ?
All right . All right . Yo , Pam ! Come on !
Tina and Eddie are gonna show up the minute they get hungry ,
so stop worrying .
I 'm not worried anymore . I 'm just pissed .
Stop it .
Look , why don 't you take Tommy with you ?
It 'll probably do him good to get him out of here for a while .
Yeah , that 's a good idea .
Tommy ! Pam 's taking Reggie to see his brother tonight .
Why don 't you ride along with them ?
Yeah ! Great idea . Now , let 's go .
Why don 't you go see what you can do ?
Okay .
Tommy .
Come on . It 'll be fun .
Okay ?
Good .
Come on .
No . I 'll wait here .
I 'm okay .
[ REGGIE BANGING ON DOOR ]
REGGIE : Yo , Demon !
DEMON : Is that the big bad wolf rapping on my door ?
Yeah , bro . It 's me . It 's me . Open up !
That you , Reckless ?
Open up the door !
Oh , my God ! Well , get your ass in here , boy !
God , it 's good to see you , dude !
Damn , you look good !
I know , I know .
Oh , God . Look at this . God !
Hey , you had any dinner ?
Here . Have an enchilada . Man .
Wow , man ! Where 'd you get those bad rings from ?
If you 've been around the world as long as your big brother have ,
you get things .
Freaking A ! Where 'd you get that ?
Hey , calm down , dude . Hey , say hello to Anita . She 's my girlfriend .
Hello , beautiful .
[ LAUGHING ] Hey , little brother , what 's happening ?
Listen , I want you all to meet somebody .
Hey , Pam ! Yo , Pam . Come here , baby , come here .
This is my friend Pam . Hi .
She 's my girlfriend .
What 's up , Pam ?
[ BUZZING ]
Pam , you hungry ? No , thanks .
You want a taco ? Egg roll ? What about a slice of pizza ?
No , thank you .
Cheese and sausage .
What about you , Brother ? I know what you want .
Want a beer ? Yeah , I 'll take ...
Get out of here .
I 'll tell you what , why don 't you take this ?
Wow !
Hey , man , this is bad !
Nothing is too good for my little brother .
You gonna give me this , too ?
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
[ MOTORCYCLE APPROACHING ]
[ JUNIOR LAUGHING ]
I got you , didn 't I ?
Really scared you , didn 't I ?
Are you dumb or something ?
You 're a crazy from the loony bin !
My mama 's going to chop you up
into itty-bitty pieces , my friend !
You hear me ?
I said , are you hearing me ?
Fuck you , lunatic !
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SHOUTING ] Tommy !
Reggie , we 've got to go now .
It 's okay , Bro . Come on .
Take care , all right ? Thanks for the dinner .
Anytime . Stay cool , baby .
Hey , stay safe , Reckless !
I will !
You know , I miss him already .
Yeah , he 's a cutie pie .
Want to hit this ?
[ GROANS ] Yeah .
What 's wrong ?
Hey , you okay ?
It 's them damn enchiladas .
You gonna be all right ?
[ GROANING ]
[ GROANS IN RELIEF ]
[ RATTLING ]
Who 's that ?
Stop it !
[ GIGGLES ]
You 're gonna get it , bitch !
Lighten up , Demon . You 'll feel a lot better after you shit .
I 'll feel a lot better when I 'm out of here .
This shit box is gross !
Well , you better watch out for the snake
that 's gonna crawl up that crapper and bite your ass .
♪ Ooh , baby , hey , baby ♪
♪ Hey , baby ♪
♪ Ooh , baby ♪
♪ Ooh , baby , baby ♪
♪ Hey , baby , hey , baby ♪
♪ Ooh , baby , ooh , baby ♪
♪ Ooh , baby ♪
Anita ? Hey , girl , what 's up ?
[ RATTLING ]
Hey !
Okay . I told you this isn 't funny .
Now you 're gonna get it , bitch .
Anita !
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ CRYING ]
[ STUTTERING ] Matt 's gone . George , too .
Are you sure ?
I looked everywhere .
And Tina and Eddie haven 't come back , either .
Where are they ?
Look , it 's okay . Calm down , Jake .
Let 's try to take this slowly .
Where did Matt say he was going ?
He didn 't .
Yes , he did .
He said he was gonna go look for Tina and Eddie .
Where 's Tommy ?
I thought he was with you .
And where 's Gramps ?
I don 't know , Reggie .
Look , why don 't you all go inside ?
I 'm gonna go find everyone .
Jake , I 'm putting you in charge .
Yes .
And you , little Reckless ,
I want you in bed asleep by the time I get back , right ?
No problem .
Okay .
[ SCREAMING ]
I 'm making your dinner , Junior !
You hearing me , fella ?
He hurt me , Ma ! Do you hear me ? They hurt me !
[ CONTINUES SCREAMING ]
I am making your dinner !
[ SPITS ]
They hurt me , Ma !
Will you murder all of them ?
Chop them and kill them ?
Do you hear me ?
Are you hearing me , boy ?
Get off that fucking bike and come here and eat my stew !
[ SCREAMING ]
[ DOOR OPENING ]
About time , you fuckwad .
I knew you couldn 't pass up on my stew .
You hearing me , Junior ?
You talk . You dumb ?
[ SCREAMS ]
[ ENGINE STALLING ]
[ EXCLAIMS IN ANGER ]
It 's so lonely here .
It 's like we were the only two people left in the whole world .
Maybe we are .
Maybe when we get back to shore ,
everybody else will have disappeared .
I 'd like that , wouldn 't you ?
Robin ?
We 've been here nearly eight months now , right ?
Uh-huh .
That 's a long time to get to know somebody , don 't you think ?
[ SHUSHING ] Jake , please .
Sure , sure .
And we could go anywhere we wanted ,
and we could live in the biggest house in the world if we wanted .
Me , I 'd like to live in a little house ,
just big enough for the two of us .
Only there 's gonna be more than two of us , isn 't there ?
[ GASPS ]
I like you , Robin .
A lot .
And I like you , too , Jake .
You do ? A lot ?
What are you talking about , Jake ?
I want to be with you .
I really do want to be with you .
I want to make love with you .
[ LAUGHING ]
I ...
I didn 't mean it .
I said I didn 't mean it !
MAN ON TV : I 'm sorry that I 've been so ...
So nasty to you .
[ THUNDERING ]
Vi !
[ MUSIC PLAYING ]
Vi , I 'd like to talk to you . Huh ?
I need to talk to you !
Can it wait ?
No .
[ GASPS ]
Reggie . Reggie ? Come on .
Reggie , wake up .
Come on . It 's time to go to bed .
Reggie , wake up . Reggie !
[ SIGHS ]
Okay , your way .
Jake , I 'm sorry .
You know , sometimes , Robin , you are just so stupid .
[ THUNDERING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GASPING ]
[ CHOKING ]
[ HIS EYES PLAYING ]
¶ There was a man so cold , no life was in his eyes
¶ He had a look so hard , I 'd never seen him smile
¶ I could 've told you then
[ DOOR BANGING ]
¶ You 'd heard it all before
¶ And now you 're in suspense , you 'll have to wait for more
¶ In all those mysteries you 're taken by surprise
¶ You never thought to see that look was in his eyes
¶ There 's a man with no life in his eyes
[ GASPS ]
[ CHOKING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ THUNDERING ]
What are them nuts up to now ?
Yo , Tommy . You back ?
Tommy , you in here ?
Yo , Tommy .
[ GASPS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
What is it , Reggie ? It 's Pam . What 's the matter ?
It 's me ! What is it ? What is it ?
In Tommy 's room !
Okay . All right . You stay here .
Relax . I 'll be right back , okay ?
[ PAM SCREAMS ]
Move !
[ SCREAMS ]
Get up ! Get up !
[ SCREAMING ]
Shit !
Run ! Come on ! Let 's go !
Go !
Help us !
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
Reggie ! Reggie !
Pam , where are you ?
Pam !
Reggie !
[ SCREAMING ]
Reggie ! Reggie !
Reggie !
[ SCREAMS ]
No ! No !
No ! No ! No !
[ SCREAMS ]
No !
[ COUGHING ]
It 's okay , Reggie . It 's okay . It 's okay .
[ CRYING ]
God .
[ SCREAMING ]
PAM : Run ! Run !
[ RATTLING ]
[ WHIRRING ]
Yeah ! All right ! Pam !
[ REGGIE CHEERING ]
Yeah ! Pam !
[ STOPS WHIRRING ]
[ SHOUTING ]
Tommy ! Tommy !
Run , Tommy , run !
Run ! He 'll kill you !
Jason ?
PAM : Listen to me !
Run ! Go ! Tommy , get out !
Jason ? PAM : Get out !
Listen ! Tommy , go !
[ HEART BEATING ]
PAM : Please , Tommy !
TRISH : Tommy !
TOMMY : Remember .
Don 't .
TOMMY : Remember . Die !
Remember . Die !
Jason .
TOMMY : Remember , remember .
Remember , remember , remember ...
PAM : Tommy ! Tommy !
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
Up here , Tommy ! Come on ! Up here !
Come on ! Come on !
Tommy , please !
REGGIE : Come on , Tommy , up here !
PAM : Come on !
REGGIE : Come on ! Hurry up !
Tommy , hurry up ! PAM : Come on , please .
Come on , come on !
REGGIE : Come on , Tommy ! You can do it ! Come on , Tommy !
PAM : Tommy , please !
REGGIE : No , come on , Tommy . Hurry up !
PAM : Take my hand . Take my hand !
REGGIE : You can do it . Yeah , come on . Yeah .
Come on , yeah ! REGGIE : One more ! Just one more , Tommy .
REGGIE : Come on !
Come on , you can do it !
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
REGGIE : No ! Please , don 't kill me ! No !
Pam , help me ! Pam ! Come on , Pam !
No ! Pam !
Please ! Please , somebody help me ! Pam !
[ SCREAMS ]
How are you doing ?
Quite a kid .
We found this on Roy .
The kid who was axed to death at the wood pile was Roy 's son .
God only knows why Roy kept it
hidden all these years , but he did .
Roy was a real loner .
Never talked much , not even to the other paramedics .
I guess when he was called to the scene
and he saw that it was his own Joey all hacked to pieces ...
We also found these .
I guess he used the Jason thing to
cover up with .
Tommy .
Hi .
[ GASPS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
[ GASPS ]
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
[ GLASS BREAKING ]
Oh , my God .